In our next exercise, we're going to examine tool tips and
在这个练习里 我们将会学习 工具提示和模态框
modals and how we can add these to our page.
以及学习如何将它们应用到我们的网页中
We're gonna go to the index.html page that we have been designing so
我们要做的是修改我们的
far on our website.
index.html 文件
And we're going to add a tooltip and we're also going to add a modal to this webpage.
我们将在其中加进 一个工具提示和一个模态框
You will also explore modals in more detail in the assignment that
对于模态框更详细的内容 你将会在接下来的
follows at the end of this module.
大作业中遇到
Going to our webpage.
来到我们的网页
We see that in the index.html file, we have this button here.
你可以看到这里 有一个 Reserve Table 的按钮
I would like to introduce a tooltip for the button so
我将会为这个按钮实现一个工具提示
that when you hover on that button, then a tooltip will pop up.
从而当你将鼠标悬停其上时 你能看到一个工具提示显现出来
In addition, we have a form in the navbar which was used for signing in.
此外 我还要把导航栏 右侧这个登录表格
I'm gooing to shift that form into a modal.
移到一个模态框中
So that you only have a login button there and when you click on that login,
从而右侧这里将只剩一个 login 按钮 当你点击该按钮时
then that modal will pop up and allow you to enter your username and
一个模态框将会弹出 其中所含内容正是那登录表格
password and then login to the website.
于是你可以通过它来登录
To introduce a tooltip into a website in the index.html file,
为了在 index.html 中实现工具提示
they will navigate down to the jumbotron which contains that button.
我们需要找到我们实现 Reserve Table 按钮的地方
For the button I'm going to introduce a tooltip into the a tag
它位于我们实现超大屏幕之处 可以看到 我们是用 a 标签来实现的
which represents that button.
而实现工具提示的方法 就是对这个 a 标签设置一些额外的属性
Let me introduce the code and then we'll come back and
现在先让我将代码贴好 然后我们再来看
examine that code in a little more detail and then see the result on the web page.
我贴的代码是怎么运作的
Here you see that I have already introduced
那么有了这些代码
the tooltip to the a tag in the jumbotron.
工具提示就已经实现好了
So to introduce a tooltip I have introduced a data-toggle, the tooltip,
你可以看到 我对这个 a 标签 设置了 data-toggle="tooltip"
and also, given in the title attribute,
然后同时 设置了 title 属性
I have given the information that should be displayed in the tooltip there.
title 属性对应的字符串 正是该工具提示将要显示的内容
To activate tooltip, you remember that we have to
为了激活该工具提示
add appropriate JavaScript code to the page.
不要忘记我们还要 加进一些 JavaScript 代码
So let's go to the bottom of the webpage and then add the correct JavaScript code.
所以让我们去到这整个文件的底部 并加进合适的 JavaScript 代码吧
I have now added the code, the JavaScript code,
在屏幕上被框住的部分 就是我们要加的 JavaScript 代码
in order to activate the tooltip here.
这些代码就能激活我们 之前实现的工具提示
So in this JavaScript code you see that when the document is ready.
这个代码的意思就是 当整个 document 准备好后
And for this data-toggle="tooltip",
将所有设置了
wherever you have this included as an attribute for
data-toggle="tooltip" 的元素
the element and will activate the tooltip.
激活为一个工具提示
So after making these changes, let's save the changes and then we'll go back and
那么在做完这些工作后 让我们回到我们的网页并看看
look at the web page.
有哪些改变
Coming to the web page, you now see that when you put your cursor
回到我们的网页 你可以发现 当你将鼠标悬停于这个按钮之上时
on the button, the tooltip pops up at the bottom here.
一个工具提示显现了出来
Showing the message that we included in the title attribute of the button there.
其内容正是我们在 title 属性中 设置的内容
The button still works as a regular button, so
而这个按钮的功能则没有变化
when you click on it you can still go to the form at the bottom of the page.
当你点击该按钮时 它仍会将你带到 页面底部的表格
But the tooltip also is displayed when you just hover over that button there.
不过即使你不点击那按钮 工具提示仍会显现出来
Our next step is to introduce the modal, so
我们下一步要做的是实现一个模态框
that we can shift the login form into their modal.
从而我们能将导航栏中的登录表格 移到该模态框中
So to do that I go right up to the top and
为此 我将会在这个  下面
right after the nav element there, the navbar there.
加进一些代码
I introduce the code for the modal as specified on the workshop site,
这些代码和 Bootstrap 网站上的 模态框的示范代码很像
normally when you are using modals it is always better to include the modal code
顺便说一句 实现模态框的代码
at the top of the page.
一般最好加在一个文件的开头
So that subsequent changes in the web page
从而你对网页主体内容的修改
will not affect the modal behavior in any way.
不会影响到模态框的表现
So let me introduce the code for the modal there, and then we'll come back and
同样的 让我先把代码贴好
examine what we have done.
然后再来研究代码如何运作
Now, I have introduced the code for setting up the modal into place there.
那么框住的这些代码就是 实现模态框所需的代码
So you can see that I have an outer div, which I have given an id as the loginModal
你可以看到我对这最外层的 div 设置了 id="loginModal"
and the corresponding class as modal with the fade class also.
同时还对其设置了 class="modal fade"
Meaning that when the modal is dismissed it will fade.
意味着这将会是一个有
And when the modal is invoked, it will fade in.
渐入渐出的过渡动画效果的模态框
And inside the modal I have the class called as the model-dialog class.
然后在这个最外层 div 的下面 有一个设置了 class="modal-dialog" 的 div
And then inside the modal-dialog class I have the modal-content here.
然后再其下 还有一个设置了 class="modal-content" 的 div
So in the modal-content we will have the modal-header, body and also footer.
然后再其下 就是抬头 主体内容和页脚了
For this particular modal I am not using a footer so
在这个栗子里 我没有实现页脚 所以这里面只有两个分别设置了
I only have the modal-header and the body.
class="modal-header" 和 class="modal-body" 的两个 div
In the modal-header I am introducing
然后对于抬头 我实现了一个
a button for the closing of the modal.
用于关闭模态框的按钮
So you have a cross button there, so we have seen such button being introduced
也就是一个小叉叉 事实上用来关闭当前窗口的按钮
even for the alert class earlier, so the same kind we are using here and
一般都长成一个小叉叉的样子
then the modal-title is introduced there.
之前我们实现警告时也是这么做的
So that completes the modal-header.
那么抬头就做完了
Now the modal-body will contain the actual body of this modal.
至于主体部分 则是该模态框 主要想表达的东西
Now currently it is empty.
现在我还没塞东西进去
Now remember that I had a navbar form that I
我之前也说过
used earlier to enable the users to type in their login information.
我要将导航栏中的登录表格塞进来
So I'm going to go into the navbar and then cut out that form and
所以我要将之前放在导航栏中的一些代码
then paste it into this location and then edit that form a little bit.
剪到这里来
So to do that let's scroll back to that navbar there,
所以让我们去找那段 实现登录表格的代码吧
and then we have the form element there, so
它应当是用 form 标签包起来的一段代码
I am just going to cut the entire form element from there and
我会把这整段代码
then paste it into the modal there.
剪到我们模态框的主体内容中
So cutting out that element from there.
因为一旦模态框实现好了
We no longer need it there.
就无需再在导航栏中 塞一个登录表格了
So I'm going to take that and then paste it into the modal body here.
现在让我来做一些剪切粘贴的工作
The form can be retained as such because that is exactly what we want the form to
需注意这不会改变该表格的表现
perform.
毕竟没有变动代码
But now the form is no longer a navbar form, so
不过由于该表格已不再是 导航栏中的表格
I need to change the class to form-inline, so
所以我要将其 class 属性的设置 变更为 class="form-inline"
that their elements are displayed in line inside that modal there.
从而该表格将会在同一行中 呈现其所有内容
In addition, in the form right after the sign in button,
同时 在这个 Sign in 按钮旁边
I will also introduce a cancel button there.
我将实现一个 cancel 按钮
So if the user doesn't want to log in they can press the cancel button and
所以如果用户突然不想登录了
then dismiss the form.
他可以通过该按钮来关掉表格
So, let me introduce the code and
同样的 让我先贴好代码
then we'll have a quick look at that code there.
然后再看其原理
You can now see that I have introduced an additional button there of the class
其实这段代码很简单 就只是对一个 button 标签设置了各种属性
button type and button default.
比如 type="button" 和 class="btn btn-default btn-xm"
And the corresponding attribute there also says data-dismiss="modal",
不过那些都只是对外观的定制 重要的是要设置 data-dismiss="modal"
meaning that when this button is clicked the modal will be dismissed.
意味着点击这个按钮后 模态框会被关掉
After making these changes we now need a way of invoking the modal.
同时为了显示这个模态框
So we have to introduce another link into our
我们需要在导航栏中加进一个 相对应的链接或按钮
navbar, which when clicked will invoke the modal.
通过点击它来让模态框显示出来
So to do that I go back to the navbar there and right after the ul data,
为此 我们要在导航栏对应的代码 这里的  之下
I will introduce another nav element there.
实现另一个导航栏元素
Which will contain a list item which when clicked will invoke the modal.
这将会是一个列表元素
I have now introduced another nav element.
不过表现出来的形式 将会是我们需要的对应的链接
So here you see that I am using the ul tag with the class nav, navbar, nav.
你可以看到我用了一个 ul 标签并设置了 class="nav navbar-nav navbar-right"
But in addition, I am saying using the class navbar-right, meaning
其中 navbar-right 表示 无论该 ul 标签下面内容是什么
that whatever content in this ul will be pushed to the right side of the navbar.
都会被推到导航栏的右边
So inside this navbar I have one list item.
然后在 ul 的下面 只有一个 li 标签
This list item is the one that is going to be used
而这个 li 标签对应的东西 正是我要用来
to invoke the modal.
显示模态框的东西
So in here I am using the a tag with a data-toggle modal and
你可以看到我用了一个 a 标签 并为之设置了
the data-target as loginModal.
data-toggle="modal 和 data-target="#loginModal"
Remember that I have used loginModal as the ID for the modal that I introduced
这是因为我对之前的模态框设置了 id="loginModal"
earlier, so this is the same thing specified as the data target here.
所以为了让这个 a 标签指向那模态框 就要设置其 data-target 属性为那 id
Now inside here of course I have the login and
然后在 a 标签中就是内容的设置了 我放了一个 glyphicon 图标
then a glyphicon that I use to indicate the login there.
和"Login"这五个字母
So with these changes, let's save the file, and
那么做完这些工作后
then go back and look at the changes on our webpage.
让我们保存一下并回到我们的网页
Coming back to our webpage, in the index.html file,
来看看有什么变化
we saw that the tooltip already works when we hover onto the Reserve Table button.
我们能看到工具提示还是 很安定地发挥着功用
Now, you also see that there is a Login in the navbar there,
同时你能在导航栏右侧 看到一个 Login 链接
so let's click on the login link.
当我们点击该链接时
And when you click on the Login link you now see that
你会看到一个模态框
the modal is shown here at the top of the page here.
在页面上方显示了出来
So inside this modal is you can see that the login information can be typed in and
在这个模态框中正是一个登录表格
then you have the Sign In button.
然后这里有一个 Sign in 按钮
If you click on the Cancel button of course the Login is dismissed.
如果你点击这个 Cancel 按钮的话 这个模态框就会关掉
Similarly if you click on this cross, also the Login is dismissed.
同样的 如果你点击模态框 右上角那个小叉叉时 模态框也会被关掉
And again, walking the modal if you type in the email and password and click on
然后如果你填写好了相应的信息后
the Sign In button, then the sign in operation should be invoked at that point.
点击了这个 Sign in 按钮的话 相应的注册行为就会被激发
Currently of course, the form is not active
当然了 我们目前还没有 实现这个注册行为
because we don't have a server in place to
因为我们还没有一个服务端对 证实用户身份的支持
validate the user's identity at the moment.
以上 我们完成了这次练习 在该练习中 我们学习了如何应用
This completes this exercise where we explored tool tips and modals.
工具提示和模态框 【翻译 - Carefree0910】